Guide to the Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Development Files
  - Lists - Corporations and Companies (Box 41)
  - Mass Education Movement - Report, 1946-1947 (Box 42)
  - Medical College:
    - Chungshan (Box 42)
    - Hsiang-Ya (Box 42)
    - Lanchow (Box 42)
    - National Central - Nanking (Box 42)
    - Peking University (Box 42)
    - Shanghai University (Box 42)
  - Medical education (Box 42)
  - Medical Journals - U. S. and Editors (Box 42)
  - Memorial Funds:
    - Hu Shih Memorial Scholarship Fund (Box 42)
    - Ju David M. C. Fund (Box 42)
    - Kohlberg, Alfred Memorial Fund (Box 42)
    - Kohlberg, Alfred Memorial Fund:
      - First National City Bank of New York (Box 42)
      - General Plans for the Fund (Box 42)
      - Marvin Liebman Associates (Box 42)
      - Medical Lab NDMC Taipei (Box 42)
      - Minutes (Box 42)
      - Weekly Progress Reports (Box 42)
    - Kohlberg, Jane Memorial Fund (Box 42)
    - LLiu, Heng J. Memorial Fund (Box 42)
  - Midwifery (Box 42)
  - Morani Contributions - Plastic Surgery (Box 42)
  - Morani Thank You Letters (Box 42)
  - National Health Administration (Box 42)
  - National Institute of Health (Box 42)
  - National Student Nurses Association: (Box 43)
    - Acknowledgement Letters for Taiwan Project Contributions (Box 43)
    - Contributions (Box 43)
    - Correspondence 1957-1965, (4 Folders) (Box 43)
    - Dedication of NSNA Dormitory (Box 43)
    - Journey to Taiwan; So Others May Live (Box 43)
    - Newsletter and Presidents Letter (Box 43)
  - National Student Nurses Association: (Box 44)
    - Photographs (Box 44)
    - Taiwan Project - N.Y. State Convention (Box 44)
    - Taiwan Projects - Speeches (Box 44)
  - News Clips on China (Box 44)
  - News Releases (Box 44)
  - Nursing - Lanchow - Northwest School of (Box 44)
  - Penicillin Plant (Box 44)
  - Printing Press (Box 44)
  - Publicity and Fund Raising Materials:
    - ABMAC.Appeal Letters (Box 44)
    - ABMAC Fund Raising Letters (Box 44)
    - Annual Dinner...55th birthday of Republic of China (Box 44)
    - Approach to Foundations (Box 44)
    - Allen Lau Photography Material (Box 44)
    - Letters From Contributors (Box 44)
    - Prospective Contributors $5,000 and up (Box 44)
    - West Coast Fund Raising (Box 44)
  - Schistosomiasis (Box 44)
  - Stevens, Helen Kennedy (Box 44)
  - Streptomycin (Box 44)
  - Tuberculosis (Box 44)
- Series VI: Fellowship Name File
  Arranged chronologically and subarranged according to first letter of last name.
  - 1941-1946 (A - I) (Box 45)
  - 1941-1946 (J - Y) to 1947 (A - Cha) (Box 46)
  - 1947 (Che - Y) (Box 47)
  - 1948 (A - Y) (Box 48)
  - 1949-1950 (C - Hu) (Box 49)
  - 1949-1950 (Hua - Q) (Box 50)
  - 1949-1950 (S - Z ) (Box 51)
  - 1950-1959 (C - Chen) (Box 52)
  - 1950-1959 (Cheng - Hs) (Box 53)
  - 1950-1959 (HU K) (Box 54)
  - 1950-1959 (L - Lin) (Box 55)
  - 1950-1959 (Ling - R) (Box 56)
  - 1950-1959 (S - T) (Box 57)
  - 1950-1959 (W - Y) (Box 58)
  - 1960-1969 (C - G) (Box 59)
  - 1960-1969 (H - S) (Box 60)
  - 1960-1969 (T - Z) (Box 61)
  - 1964-1977 (Visiting Professors) (Box 62)
- Series VII: Fellowships and Program Files
  - ABMAC (Box 63)
    - Copies (Box 63)
    - Fellows Club (Box 63)
    - Fellowship and Scholarship (Box 63)
    - Fellowship Program - General information (Box 63)
  - Applications for Personal Accident Insurance (Box 63)
  - Chow is Formosa's Florence Nightingale - -By Julian Hartt (Box 63)
  - Clinical Pathology in Formosa, a Program, 1955 (Box 63)
  - Complete List of Fellowship Holders from Taiwan Sponsored by various agencies in ABMAC (Box 63)
  - Continental Development Foundation (Box 63)
  - Correspondence Fellows (Box 63)
  - Doctors in Public Health (Box 63)
  - DSP-66 Forms (Box 63)
  - Educational Council for Foreign Medical Graduates (Box 63)
  - English Center. Joint Technical Assistance Committee (Box 63)
  - Fellowship, 1946-1955 (Box 63)
  - Fellowship, 1961, 1962 (Box 63)
  - Fellowship, 1962-1963 (Box 63)
  - Fellowship applicants (Box 63)
  - Fellowship applications (Box 63)
  - Fellowship Committee Meeting, 19 December 1963 (Box 63)
  - Fellowship Folders (Box 63)
  - Fellowship Matters, 1951-1952, 1956-1957 (Box 63)
  - Fellowship Sub-Committee (Box 63)
  - Foreign Student Insurance Plan - Wm. H. Gray Company (Box 63)
  - General Fellowship Matters, 1964 (Box 63)
  - Government Grant and Aid to ABMAC Program (Box 63)
  - Harmon Foundation - Day Break Around the World (Box 63)
  - Hu, Jerome Luncheon, 13 April 1965 (Box 63)
  - Hu, Shih (Box 63)
  - Information Sheets (A- Z), (2 Folders) (Box 64)
  - Information Sheets, 1951 – 1953, (3 Folders) (Box 64)
  - Intern-Residency Travel Fellowships (Box 64)
  - International Communication Agency Exchange Visitor Program (Box 64)
  - Kohler, William (Box 64)
  - Lederle International Fellowship (Box 64)
  - Letter to Dr: Root From 1950 Fellows (Box 64)
  - Leuallen, E.E. - Albany (Box 64)
  - List of Fellows, February 1963 (Box 64)
  - Liu, Heng J. (Box 64)
  - Meeting on Fellowship Matters (Box 64)
  - Meleney Fellowships-- Gregersen Letters (Box 64)
  - Metabolism (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 64)
  - National Defense Medical Center (Box 64)
  - New York Infirmary Residency (Box 64)
  - General Information, 1965 (Box 64)
  - Notes on Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation Fellowships (Box 64)
  - Nursing Committee Meeting (Box 64)
  - Pasadena Fellowship, 1956-1957 (Box 65)
  - Peace Corps Bill, 1961 (Box 65)
  - Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Report on ABMAC Programs in Free China, 1960 (Box 65)
  - Reports of Work from 1950 Fellows (Box 65)
  - School Health Committee Meeting (Box 65)
  - Shipment File, (14 Folders) (Box 65)
  - Slide Set and Script on Army Nursing School, (2 Folders) (Box 65)
  - A Study of the 1950 Fellowship Program (Box 66)
  - U.S. Immigration and Naturalization, 1958 (Box 66)
  - U.S. Medical: Mission to Taiwan, 1968, (2 Folders) (Box 66)
  - Visiting Professor Residence, Taipei, Taiwan (Box 66)
  - Webester, Jerome P. (Box 66)
  - Wei, Huoyao (Box 66)
  - Dean of National Taiwan University College of Medicine (Box 66)
  - Williams - Waterman Fund (Box 66)
  - Withdrawals - Fellowship (Box 66)
  - Yen, C.I. (Box 66)
  - Dinner, (3 Folders) (Box 66)
  - Yen, C. K. (Mrs.) (Box 66)
  - Armstrong's Tea for (Box 66)
- Series VIII: Aid Refugee Chinese Intellectuals
  - Agenda, 1960-1969 (except 1964) (Box 67)
  - Annual Report, 1953 -1958 (Box 67)
  - Annual Report, 1960-1961 (Box 67)
  - Annual Report – Terminal Report, 21 May 1969 (Box 67)
  - By-Laws - Original and Revised (Box 67)
  - Case History, (3 Folders) (Box 67)
  - Case History from Hong Kong (Box 67)
  - Certificate of Inc., Dissolution, Tax exemptions and Registration (Box 67)
  - Correspondence; Miscellaneous (Box 67)
  - Dissolution (Box 67)
  - Explanatory Booklet (Box 67)
  - Financial Records:
    - Advisory Committee on Voluntary Foreign Aid (Box 67)
    - Audits 1952- 1969 (5 Folders except 1964) (Box 67)
  - Financial Records: (Box 68)
    - Bank Statements: 1960-1963 Hong Kong Account (Box 68)
    - Bank Statements 1965-1966 (Box 68)
    - Bank Statements 1967-1969 (Box 68)
    - Code of Accounts December 1952-1957 (Box 68)
    - Code of Accounts January 1958-1969 (Box 68)
    - Dept. of State, Reports on Collection of Loans (Box 68)
    - Intergovernmental Committee for European Migration, Reports on Collection of Loans (Box 68)
    - Journal (Box 68)
    - N.Y.S. Dept. of Social Services (Box 68)
    - U.S. Internal Revenue Service (Box 68)
    - U.S. Treasury- Quarterly Federal Tax (Box 68)
  - Liu, George Kwa-Yuen (Box 69)
  - Minutes - Executive Committee, 1952-54 (Box 69)
  - Minutes, 1955 to 1969, (3 Folders) (Box 69)
  - Pamphlet (Box 69)
  - Registrants of ARCI; Material on (Box 69)
  - Report on Past Year's Accomplishments (Box 69)
  - A Report to Our Contributors (Box 69)
  - Success Story (Box 69)
  - This is Communist Propaganda (Box 69)
  - Yang, Jenken (Box 69)
- Series IX: American Emergency Committee for Tibetan Refugees
  - Agenda, 1963 to 1969, (7 Folders) (Box 70)
  - Annual Report:
    - 1960 to 1966, (7 Folders) (Box 70)
    - Terminal Report, thru 6/30/69 (Box 70)
  - Appeal Letters (Box 70)
  - By-Laws - Original, and Amended (Box 70)
  - Certificate of Dissolution (Box 70)
  - Certificate of Incorporation - Original and Amended (Box 70)
  - Correspondence; Miscellaneous (Box 70)
  - Dissolution (Box 70)
  - Financial Records:
    - Advisory Committee on Voluntary foreign Aid (Box 70)
    - Audits - Indian Office (Box 70)
    - Audits - New York Office (Box 70)
    - Brunetti, Arhtur H. (Box 70)
    - Check Stubs (Box 70)
    - Coleman, Betty J. (Box 70)
  - Financial Records: (Box 71)
    - Financial Statements (Box 71)
    - Fletcher, Travis L. (Box 71)
    - Form 990-A - Organization Exempt form Income Tax (Box 71)
    - Indian Office Account (Box 71)
    - Insurance (Box 71)
    - McDonald, Patricia (Box 71)
    - Memorandum: 1961-1968 (Box 71)
    - New York State Dept. of Social Services Annual Report (Box 71)
    - Payroll (Box 71)
    - Shurtleff, Norene (Box 71)
    - Tax - Matters (Box 71)
    - Tax exemption Certificates (Box 71)
    - Toulouse, John D. (Box 71)
    - United State Dept. of Commerce Quarterly Reports (Box 71)
    - Working Papers (Box 71)
  - Minutes (1959-1969 ) 2 Folders (Box 71)
  - New York State Dept. of Law - Annual Reports (Box 71)
  - Reports and Mailing Enclosure (Box 71)
- Series X: Free China Fund
  - Advisory Committee on Voluntary Foreign Aid (Box 72)
  - Donor`s Lists Joint Dinner, 2 June 1955 (Box 72)
  - National Better Business Bureau (Box 72)
  - National City Bank of New York (Box 72)
  - National Information Bureau (Box 72)
  - New York State Reports of Various Departments (Box 72)
  - Oram Office Correspondence (Box 72)
  - Publicity and Reports:
    - The Free China Fund, (2 Folders) (Box 72)
    - The Free China Fund - Fact Sheet Mailings (1954-1961) 2 Folders (Box 72)
    - Medical and Refugee (Box 72)
    - Aid No Greater Sacrifice Forgotten? Only if You Forget them (Box 72)
    - Our Answer to Communist False Promises... (Box 72)
    - Picture Sheets (Box 72)
    - Report - Special Assistance to Chinese National Red Cross (Box 72)
    - Thank You, America -- Three Nurses at Yale (Box 72)
    - The Trained., the Trainee (Box 72)
    - What has Been Done by the Free China Fund (Box 72)
    - What is the Free China Fund (Box 72)
  - Sponsor Acceptance A-G (Box 72)
  - Sponsor Acceptance H-Z (Box 72)
  - Sponsor. Memos to (Box 72)
  - United States. Dept. of Treasury (Box 72)
  - United States. Internal Revenue Service - Form 990-A (Box 72)
- Series XI: United China Relief and Subject File
  - Chiang Kai-Shek (Mme.) Address to the House of Representatives (Box 73)
  - Chiang Kai- Shek Letter to (Box 73)
  - China Emergency Relief Committee, Inc., 1941 (Box 73)
  - Constitution (Box 73)
  - Financial Records - Audits Reports, 1941-1943 [5 Folders] (Box 73)
  - Office Memos (Box 73)
- Series XII: United Service to China: Subject File
  - Annual Reports, 1941-1947 (Box 74)
  - Continental Associates, Inc. (Box 74)
  - Cromwell, Nelson William, Estate of (Box 74)
  - Financial Records:
    - Audit, Reports, 1941-1956, (2 Folders) (Box 74)
    - Financial Statements (Box 74)
  - Hazard, Marion G. (Box 74)
  - History (Box 74)
  - Lists--Board of Directors (Box 74)
  - Minutes, 1955-1966 (Box 74)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 74)
  - Printed Material - An Evening of Western Music (Box 74)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia (Box 74)
- Series XIII: Photographs
  - Air Raid Shelter (Box 75)
  - Air Raid Victims (Box 75)
  - ABMAC No. 1-4., (4 Folders) (Box 75)
  - ABMAC No. 5 (Box 76)
  - ABMAC Ambulance Book I (Box 76)
  - ABMAC China Office (Box 76)
  - ABMAC Miscellaneous U.S. (Box 76)
  - ABMAC Pictures (Box 76)
  - ABMAC Village for NDMC Faculty and Families (Box 76)
  - American Emergency Committee for Tibetan Refugees, (2 Folders) (Box 77)
  - Anti-Malaria Unit - Fang Shan Military Camps (Box 77)
  - Army Medical Administration No. 1-3, (4 Folders) (Box 77)
  - Army Medical Administration No. 4 (Box 78)
  - Army Medical Center EMSTS (Box 78)
  - Army Medical Center Kiangwan, Shanghai (Box 78)
  - Army Orthopedic Center (Box 78)
  - Blankets (Box 78)
  - Bowl of Rice Ball – 1940 (Box 78)
  - Bowl of Rice Pictures (Box 78)
  - Boy Scouts (Box 78)
  - Burma Road (Box 78)
  - Canal (Box 78)
  - Canton General Hospital (Box 78)
  - Chang Kai-Shek, Mme. (Box 78)
  - Children (Box 78)
  - Chinese Blood Bank - B 1 to 50 (Box 78)
  - Chinese Blood Bank - B 51 to 90 (Box 78)
  - Chinese National Relief and Rehabilitation Administration (Box 79)
  - Chinese News Service (Box 79)
  - Chinese Opera (Box 79)
  - Chinese Zither (Box 79)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 79)
  - Church (Box 79)
  - Clothing (Box 79)
  - Conference: ABMAC Medical, International Health (Box 79)
  - Cooking School (Box 79)
  - Correspondence - Photos Display (Box 79)
  - Culture - Art, Dance, Opera (Box 79)
  - Debutante Pictures (Box 79)
  - Debutantes UCR Waldorf Dinner (Box 79)
  - Delta, Delta, Delta (Box 79)
  - Dentistry (Box 79)
  - Destruction - Chungking (Box 79)
  - Dime a Shine - Pictures (Box 79)
  - Display Life's United Nations (Box 79)
  - Eisenhower Dwight in Taiwan (Box 79)
  - Ekins (Box 79)
  - Faces of Men (Box 79)
  - Face of Women (Box 79)
  - Famine in Hunan China (Box 79)
  - Farming (Box 79)
  - Fashions (Box 79)
  - Fellowship (Box 79)
  - Festival (Box 79)
  - First Aid Stations (Box 79)
  - Gelatine Project (Box 80)
  - Government (Box 80)
  - Gourielli Shop (Box 80)
  - Grand Central Palace Exhibit (Box 80)
  - Hankemeyer, Natalie (Box 80)
  - Health Station Clinics (Box 80)
  - Honorable Moon Picture - Shirley Temple (Box 80)
  - Hospitals (Box 80)
  - Hospital Raises Funds for UCR (Box 80)
  - Hospital Wards (Box 80)
  - Hsiang-Ya (Box 80)
  - Yale in China (Box 80)
  - Hsin, Cheng (Box 80)
  - Rehabilitation Center (Box 80)
  - Hughes, Edith & Walt Disney 80 (Box 80)
  - Hyatt Glee Club Recording "San Min Chui" at Carl Fischer Studios (Box 80)
  - Hyatt Glee Club at Work, General Motors (Box 80)
  - Identification Buttons Pictures (Box 80)
  - Indusco Display (Box 80)
  - Indusco "Kung Ho Party" (Box 80)
  - Indusco Photos (Box 80)
  - Industry Inter-Faith Convocation (Box 80)
  - IBM (Box 80)
  - July 7, 1942 (Box 80)
  - Kite Party (Box 80)
  - Kohlberg, Alfred Laboratory (Box 81)
  - Laboratories (Box 81)
  - Lanchow, China (Box 81)
  - Lanchow - Medical Center, Nursing and General (Box 81)
  - Levering, Griffith G. (Box 81)
  - Li Guan-Yuen (Box 81)
  - Li Shu-Pei (Box 81)
  - Lim, Robert K.S. (Box 81)
  - Lin, Philip (Box 81)
  - Liu, Bangnee Alfred - Biographies (Box 81)
  - Liu, Liang-Mo (Box 81)
  - Liu, Chen Wei-Giang (Box 81)
  - Luces, Henry - Tea (Box 81)
  - Luncheon Hotel Warwick (Box 81)
  - Luncheon Rainbow Grill (Box 81)
  - Macy's - Bridge to Yinhsi (Box 81)
  - Maffett Residence (Box 81)
  - Madison Square Garden Rally, New York, 2 October 1941 (Box 81)
  - Maps and Charts (Box 81)
  - Medical (Box 81)
  - Medical (School, Classes, Hospital) (Box 81)
  - Medical and Surgical Relief Committee (Box 81)
  - Meiling Marigold (Box 81)
  - Micro-Film (Box 81)
  - Midwifery (Box 81)
  - Midwifery:
    - Central Hospital Nanking (Box 81)
    - First National School Peiping (Box 81)
    - Kiangsi Province (Box 81)
  - Miscellaneous ( no. 1) (Box 81)
  - Miscellaneous (2 Folders Nos. 2 & 3) (Box 82)
  - Motion Pictures (Box 82)
  - Music - Organist at Grand Central USO (Box 82)
  - Nanking Medical Center 82 (Box 82)
  - Nanking Photos - CNS (Box 82)
  - National Defense Medical Center, (2 Folders) (Box 82)
  - National Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs (Box 83)
  - National Health Administration and Nursing (Box 83)
  - National Institute of Health National (Box 83)
  - Medical College - Shanghai (Box 83)
  - National Student Nurses Association (Box 83)
  - National Taiwan University Medical College, Hospital Nursing School Pictures (Box 83)
  - Navy Relief Dinner (Box 83)
  - New York City Committee (Box 83)
  - New York City Pictures (Special) (Box 83)
  - Newspaper Name Contest (Box 83)
  - Nursery School - Moore Memorial Church, Shanghai (Box 83)
  - Nurses Bazaar, Taipei (Box 83)
  - Nursing - Army Nursing School (Box 83)
  - Nursing Schools in Szechuan, China (Box 83)
  - Office Pictures (Box 83)
  - Office Staff (Box 83)
  - Operations - Operating Rooms (Box 83)
  - Orphans (Box 83)
  - Panda Expedition (Box 83)
  - Panda Name Contest (Box 83)
  - Panda Soap (Box 83)
  - Parades - (ABMAC) (Box 84)
  - Parade:
    - May 25th 1941 (Box 84)
    - July 7 (Box 84)
    - October 10, 1941 (Box 84)
    - National War Fund 11/43 (Box 84)
  - Pea Soup Sent to China (Box 84)
  - Peking University Medical College (Box 84)
  - Peng hu - Kingmen (Box 84)
  - Penicillin (Box 84)
  - Penthouse Party (Box 84)
  - Personalities (Box 84)
  - Photo Policy (Box 84)
  - Picture Exhibit (Box 84)
  - Pierre Roof Fashion Show (Box 84)
  - Pirie. Robert S. (Mrs.) (Box 84)
  - Proofs (Box 84)
  - Public Health (Box 84)
  - Puppet Show (Box 84)
  - Pyrogen - Free Fluid Plant, Shanghai, 1946 (Box 84)
  - Quizz Kids (Box 84)
  - Radio Show Rehearsal, 11 April 1942 (Box 84)
  - Red Cross Service and Units (Box 84)
  - Red Gate Players (Box 84)
  - Refugees - General (Box 84)
  - Refugees - Miscellaneous (Box 84)
  - Ripley Pictures (Box 84)
  - Sapiro Photos - Purchased by UCR (Box 85)
  - Scarsdale Committee Shop (Box 85)
  - School Health Program, Taipei (Box 85)
  - Schools of Medicine- Pharmacy (Box 85)
  - Screens display of 1944 (Box 85)
  - Secretarial Committee (Box 85)
  - Seng Mou-Yeh Orphanage (Box 85)
  - Shunman Dam (Box 85)
  - Silver Shoe (Box 85)
  - So Others May Live - Motion-Picture Titles (Box 85)
  - Soldiers (Box 85)
  - Soldiers- Wounded (Box 85)
  - Soroptimists (Box 85)
  - Stevens., Helen Kennedy (Box 85)
  - Street Drive, October 1942 (Box 85)
  - Street Scenes (Box 85)
  - Streptomycin (Box 85)
  - Students - Miscellaneous (Box 85)
  - Surgical Relief Supplies (Box 85)
  - Taiwan - Army Nursing School and AMC Fellows (Box 85)
  - Taiwan Medical Facilities and Miscellaneous (Box 85)
  - Taiwan Provincial School of Nursing and Midwifery (Box 85)
  - Tea (Box 85)
  - Tea for Girl Scouts - Diorama Exhibit, China House, 1948 (Box 85)
  - Telephone - First Call to China (Box 85)
  - Television-Broadcast- CBS (Box 85)
  - ""Tet" Chinese Game Played by Le Ya Ching and Service Men at USO Centre (Box 85)
  - Thumbs Up (Box 85)
  - Toys for China, China Aid Council (Box 85)
  - Triple Seven Anniversary, City Hall, 7 July 1944 (Box 85)
  - Twin Appeal (Box 85)
  - United China Relief Ambulance
    - Chinese Staffs, World Telegram Pictures (Box 85)
    - Emblem (Box 85)
    - Shop (Box 85)
    - Staff Sampling Dehydrated Food (Box 85)
  - United Nations Pictures (Box 85)
  - United Service to China - Shanghai to Plan for Child Care Conference, 4-9 November 1946 (Box 86)
  - United Service to China Institute (Box 86)
  - Unknown (Box 86)
  - "V" for Victory Pictures (Box 86)
  - V.J. Day Chinatown N,Y. (Box 86)
  - Vaccine Plant (Box 86)
  - Victory Valentine (Box 86)
  - Waldorf – Dinner, New York, 10 October 1944, (2 Folders) (Box 86)
  - Waldorf Dinner for H.H. Kung (Box 86)
  - Waldorf Dinner Photos (Box 86)
  - War Fund Conference at Waldorf (Box 86)
  - War Orphans (Box 86)
  - War Worker of the Week, 1944 (Box 86)
  - What Li Wen Saw (Box 86)
  - Williams R. R. (Box 86)
  - Window Displays for China Relief (Box 86)
  - Window Display, New York (Box 86)
  - Women's International Exposition, 1942-1947, (5 Folders) (Box 86)
  - World's Fair - Chinese Art Objects and Other Exhibits (Box 86)
  - World's Fair, New York (Box 86)
  - Writers Pledge Support (Box 86)
  - Yankee Stadium (Box 86)
  - Yellow River Project (Box 86)
  - Yenging Photos (Box 86)
  - Yinhsi - Shashi District., Tachang County China (Box 86)
  - Yinshi Village China (Box 86)
  - Yinhsi Village - Kindergarten Class (Box 86)
  - Youth Orchestra (Box 86)
  - Yu Tsai School. Shanghai (Box 86)
  - Yutang's Lin Tea Party (Box 86)
  - Photograph Negatives (Box 87)
- Series XIV: Printed Materials
  - ABMAC Publications: (Box 88)
    - Annual Reports, 1955-1978 (Box 88)
    - Booklets (Box 88)
    - Newsletters, 1950-1953 (Box 88)
  - American Emergency Committee for Tibetan Refugees: (Box 89)
    - Central Relief Committee (India) Bulletins (Box 89)
    - Miracles of Friendship (Box 89)
    - Miscellaneous News of Tibet (Box 89)
    - News Letter - Dalai Lama (Box 89)
    - News Letter - Tibet Society, of the United Kingdom, London (Box 89)
  - News-Tibet (Box 89)
  - New York (Box 89)
  - Rape of Tibet (Reader's Digest Reprint) (Box 89)
  - Rape of Tibet (This Week Magazine Reprint) (Box 89)
  - Terror in Tibet (Reader's Digest Reprint) (Box 89)
  - Tibetan Newsletter (Box 89)
  - Tibetan Refugee Health Program in India (Box 89)
  - Tibetan Refugees Handicrafts Centre at Dalhousie (Box 89)
  - Tibetan Review (Box 89)
  - China: (Box 90)
    - Clippings in Chinese, 1946 & 1947 (Box 90)
    - Internal (Box 90)
    - Chinese Musical Scores (Box 90)
    - Chinese Song Books, (2 Folders) (Box 90)
  - Committee of One Million: (Box 91)
    - Chiang Kai-Shek, Death of (Box 91)
    - Chiang Kai-Shek, Speeches and Messages (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box 91)
    - Chinese Delegation to the UN -- Speeches and articles (Box 91)
    - Committee of One Million Publications (Box 91)
    - Congressional Reports and Statements, Red China Policy (Box 91)
    - Co Tui, Frank (Box 91)
    - Duvall, Jo (Box 91)
    - Fitch, Geraldine (Box 91)
    - Garside, Bettis Alston (Box 91)
    - Gregersen., Magnus I. (Box 91)
    - Grew, Joseph C. (Box 91)
    - Hornbeck, Stanley K. (Box 91)
    - Hsia, David Y.Y. (Box 91)
    - Hu, Shih (Box 91)
    - Judd, Walter H. (Box 91)
    - Lau, Allen (Box 91)
    - Mao Tse-Tung (Box 91)
    - Maurer, Herrymon (Box 91)
    - Mills, Fmma De Long (Box 91)
    - New York Journal American (Box 91)
  - Committee of One Million: (Box 92)
    - Reasons Why Peiping Gov't. Should not be Recognized... (Box 92)
    - Root, Walter S. (Box 92)
    - Severinghaus, Aura E. (Box 92)
    - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia (Box 92)
    - Walker, Richard L. (Box 92)
    - Wang, Mark K. H. (Box 92)
    - Yeh, George K.C. (Box 92)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material on China (Box 92)
  - United China Relief: (Box 93)
    - Annual Reports (Box 93)
    - The Bamboo Telegraph (Box 93)
    - Book: "Who Will Volunteer?" and Brochure (Box 93)
    - Chinese National Anthem and Chea Lai (Arise) (Box 93)
    - News of China (1942-1946) 5 Folders (Box 93)
    - Pamphlets, (2 Folders) (Box 93)
  - 1985 Addition:
    - Medicine on a Mission: A History of the American Bureau for Medical Aid to China, Inc., 1937-1954 (Box 93)
    - NDMC School of Nursing, History (Box 93)
  - 1985 Addition: (Box 94)
    - Photographs
      - ABMAC - China Pictures, General (1) (Box 94)
      - ABMAC - China Pictures, General (2) (Box 94)
      - Ambulances (Box 94)
      - Blood Bank, New York City (Box 94)
      - Bowl of Rice Party, 1939 (Box 94)
      - Directors (Box 94)
      - Epidemic Control (Box 94)
      - Litters - carrying wounded (Box 94)
      - Nanking NHA (Box 94)
      - [National] Shanghai Medical College (Box 94)
      - Personalities (Box 94)
      - Shanghai Army Medical Center (Box 94)
- Series XV: 1986 Addition
  - ABMAC Minutes (including related letters and financial reports), 1938-1940 (Box 95)
  - Minutes, 1941-May 1942 (Box 96)
  - Minutes, June 1942-May 1943 (Box 97)
  - Minutes, June 1943-1944 (Box 98)
  - Minutes, 1945 (Box 99)
  - Minutes, 1946- June 8, 1948 (Box 100)
  - Minutes, June 23, 1948-1949 (Box 101)
  - Minutes, 1950-1953 (Box 102)